managementconsulted.com 2014-12-18

# Privacy Policy - Management Consulted

**Privacy Policy**

This website (“Management Consulted”) recognizes that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and takes your privacy seriously. Management Consulted provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using http://www.managementconsulted.com and any of its services.

**What This Policy Covers**

This policy covers Management Consulted’s treatment of personally identifiable information that Management Consulted gathers when you are accessing managementconsulted.com and when you use our services. Personally identifiable information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Management Consulted does not own or control, or to individuals that Management Consulted does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

**General**

We receive and store any information you enter on managementconsulted.com or provide to us in any other way. You may choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take full advantage of our services. The personal information you provide is used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain information, customizing the advertising and content you receive, and communicating with you about specials and new features. You may modify or remove any of your personal information at any time by logging into your account and accessing features to edit your profile and account information.

**Cookies**

When you visit managementconsulted.com, we may send one or more cookies – a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric identifiers – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. This will tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, we strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated.

**Confidentiality and Security**

Personally identifiable information about our users is an integral part of our business. While we neither rent nor sell your personal information (e.g., telephone numbers) to anyone, without your expressed consent, we will utilize such information for our services and may share this information on an anonymous basis (no disclosure of name, telephone number or e-mail address) with affiliated business to customize the information, advertising and content you receive. 

**Protection of Management Consulted and Others**

We may release personally identifiable information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Management Consulted, our employees, our users, or others. This includes, without limitation, exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

**Your Choices**

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain Management Consulted features and services. You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Management Consulted may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Management Consulted account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Questions or Concerns**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at managementconsulted.com, please contact us. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
